<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lemon Zest</title>
    <link>https://leo-p.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lemon Zest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 17:13:48 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leo-p.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Layer Wise Relevance Propagation</title>
      <link>https://leo-p.github.io/post/papers/2019-10-29-layer-wise-relevance-propagation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 17:13:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leo-p.github.io/post/papers/2019-10-29-layer-wise-relevance-propagation/</guid>
      <description>️️️⭐️️️️️⭐️⭐️ | Towards best practice in explaining neural network decisions with LRP arXiv, GitHub  The LRP or Layer-wise Relevance Propagation aims to explain which parts of an image matter. They achieve this by using a backpropagation where neurons that contribute the most received an increased weight.
 Layer-wise Relevance Propagation   This technique is very useful for images but also for other network or methodologies.
 Meaningful parts of the image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extremal Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://leo-p.github.io/post/papers/2019-10-29-extremal-perturbations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 16:46:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leo-p.github.io/post/papers/2019-10-29-extremal-perturbations/</guid>
      <description>️️️️⭐️️️️️️️⭐️️️️️️️️⭐️️️️️⭐️⭐️ | Understanding Deep Networks via Extremal Perturbations and Smooth Masks arXiv, GitHub  Very cool paper diving into interpretability! They identify the most relevant parts of an image for a classifier. Or said differently, the parts that best explain the prediction score.
Instead of the traditional approach of a rolling occlusion mask they instead 1) select a zone, 2) blur the rest of the image and 3) compute the prediction score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICCV 2019</title>
      <link>https://leo-p.github.io/post/2019-10-27-best-of-iccv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leo-p.github.io/post/2019-10-27-best-of-iccv/</guid>
      <description>The best of the 2019 International Conference on Computer Vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Teach You to Be Rich - Ramit Sethi</title>
      <link>https://leo-p.github.io/post/books/2019-10-26-i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leo-p.github.io/post/books/2019-10-26-i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich/</guid>
      <description>⭐️⭐️️️️⭐️⭐️ | I Will Teach You to Be Rich - Ramit Sethi   On the second edition of the book, Ramit goes over everything that makes up your personal finance. This book is cleary aimed for the american crowd, with a large chunk of it dediacted to credit card debt management and psychology. This is the section that least interested me.
On the other hand, what I particularly love is that this book explains the promise and pitfalls of a lot of US financial products: credit card, checking account, saving account, 401K, Roth IRA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mac setup</title>
      <link>https://leo-p.github.io/post/2019-10-25-new-mac-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 09:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leo-p.github.io/post/2019-10-25-new-mac-setup/</guid>
      <description>I lost everything on my Mac, so here is a reinstallation from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>